

7 Vandewater St #303, San Francisco 94133, CA

□ 404 988 8702 |
■ vojtech@miksu.cz |
miksu.cz |
oda tajo |
miksu

Summary_

Current Front End Engineer at Cloudflare, San Francisco. 4+ years experience of designing and creating big web applications using libraries as React and tools as Webpack. My focus is to build a platform to enable other engineers contribute faster and scale our efforts. I thrive on diverse and multidisciplinary teams. A good UI design and consistency is must. I have a background in Computer Science and Information Security.

Work Experience ____

Cloudflare San Francisco, CA

FRONT END ENGINEER

Jan. 2017 - PRESENT

- · Driving products as Shared Account Access, On-boarding Redesign and Billing Redesign through planning, implementation and release cycle.
- Driving incremental migration from Backbone/Marionette/Gulp/Karma to React/Redux/TypeScript/Webpack/Jest.
- Replacing routing with react-router and implementing better access control.
- Building a component library cf-ui, deploying and evangelizing CSS in JS.
- · Leading modularization of the main dashboard application with Lerna and Yarn Workspaces. Creating a framework used by multiple internal applications.
- Implementing tools to remove any gap between engineers and designers.

Cloudflare San Francisco, CA

WEB ENGINEER INTERN May. 2016 - Aug. 2016

- Implemented JSON Schema powered documentation generator. Open sourced as doca.
- · Switched the main dashboard application's build process from Browserify and custom scripts to Webpack and Babel.

Wikidi Prague, Czech Republic

FRONT END ENGINEER

- · Lead developer at Flowreader.com. Working mostly remotely.
- Driving various product/feature work.
- · Executed migration from CoffeeScript, Google Closure Library and Closure Compiler to Babel, React, Flux and Browserify.

Westinghouse Electric Company

Windsor, CT

SOFTWARE ENGINEER INTERN

Jun. 2013 - Aug. 2013

Oct. 2013 - Mar. 2016

• Developed a graphical user interface for a nuclear plant simulator.

Education

Georgia Institute of Technology

Atlanta, Georgia

M.S. IN INFORMATION SECURITY

2015 - 2016

- · Receiver of Naumann-Etienne Foundation Scholarship.
- Focusing on network security and DNS datasets visualizations.

Czech Technical University

Prague, Czech Republic

B.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

2010 - 2014

2015 - PRESENT

- Spent one year at MSOE, Milwaukee, WI as an exchange student.
- · Focusing on machine learning and deep learning.

Projects

Priznej.cz Czech Republic

2013 - 2014 CREATOR

- A fun social project used by students of the 22 biggest Czech colleges.
- · Gained a huge traction over 100 000 fans in the first week and 500 000 in 3 months. It was covered by all national media.
- · Sold in June 2014.

AUTHOR

Dzejes.cz Czech Republic

- A popular series of Czech articles about modern JavaScript web development.
- About libraries and patterns like Webpack, React, Flux and Immutable.js.
- It is open sourced and github hosted: github.com/tajo/javascript.